

Senior Web Developer specializing in front end development. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. Well-versed in numerous programming languages including HTML5, PHP, JavaScript, CSS, MySQL. Strong background in project management and customer relations.

TAUSEEF TUFAIL

Phone:

- +92344 5411191
- +92355 6195249

E-Mail:

tauseefraja28@gmail.com

Address:

Khad Brahmna P/O Anderla Kotera Teh. Khuiratta, Dist. Kotli AJK, Pakistan

Skill Highlights

- CSS3
- HTML5
- iQuery
- JavaScript
- PHP
- MySQL
- WordPress
- Photoshop

Languages

English - Fluent Urdu

Portfolio/Profile

https://tauseefraja28.github.io/

Experience

Duration: 2012 to 2015 www.pearl-soft.com

Frontend Developer: Pearl-Soft Pvt. Limited Company

Started the company on internship. Then was hired by company as front end developer. Got a great experience of working in HTML, CSS, JQuery, JavaScript and Photoshop. Later on got great experience of working in WordPress, php and mySql during my stay in this company.

Duration: 2015 to 2022 www.crystalimpactwebsolutions.com

Full Stack Developer: Crystal Impact Web Solutions UAE

I am working remotely as Full Stack Developer in the company. Developed more than 100 Website projects in this company. Managed all the work load as a single developer and provided each and every project before due date. Also managed the hosting accounts for all these websites.

2007-2011

Education

BS(IT) University of AJ&K , Kotli Campus

CGPA 3.52

Certifications

Course PHP Web Application Developer Course

Institute EVS Rawalpindi

References

References available on request